Hi, I'm Chris.
こんにちは Chris です
&gt;&gt; Hi, I'm Trinh.
&gt;&gt; こんにちは トリンです
Nice to meet you.
はじめまして
&gt;&gt; Nice to meet you too.
&gt;&gt; はじめまして
Are you a software engineer?
ソフトウェアエンジニアですか?
&gt;&gt; No, actually, I'm a technical recruiter at Udacity.
&gt;&gt; いいえ 実際は Udacity のテクニカル人材採用担当者です
&gt;&gt; Cool, I actually really like Udacity.
&gt;&gt; すごいですね 実は Udacity が大好きなんです
I'm taking a number of Udacity's online courses.
Udacity のオンラインコース をいくつか受講しているんです
You guys have really helped me learn at my own pace.
自分のペースで学習できて とても身になっています
And I love that I have a flexible learning time.
それにいつでも学習できるところも 気に入っています
&gt;&gt; That's really awesome to hear.
&gt;&gt; そう言ってもらえると嬉しいです
Which projects have you been working on?
どのプロジェクトに携わっているのですか?
&gt;&gt; So I actually recently was building an application.
&gt;&gt; 最近はアプリケーションの 構築を行ってました
That let's teachers share student responses anonymously.
先生が生徒の回答を 匿名で共有できるんです
And it's been going really well.
とてもうまくいっています
I'm trying to actually add in graphic UL.
グラフィックのULを 挿入しようとしているところです
Which is a fairly recent technology.
まさに最近の技術です
So that way I can query the data a little bit easier.
これだと もう少し簡単に データをクエリできるようになるんです
&gt;&gt; It's actually pretty funny that you mentioned working on an app like that.
&gt;&gt; そのようなアプリに携わっているってきいて ちょっと面白いなって
Because Udacity is looking into developing something similar.
というのは Udacity も同じようなものの 開発を検討しているところなので
&gt;&gt; Very cool!
&gt;&gt; へぇー
Could I get your card?
名刺いただけますか?
&gt;&gt; Yeah, of course.
&gt;&gt; ええ もちろんです
I'd really love to hear from you.
連絡お待ちしています
So send me an email after this mixer.
このミーティングの後 ぜひメールくださいね
&gt;&gt; Great, thanks so much, nice to meet you.
&gt;&gt;ぜひ ありがとうございました 今後ともよろしくお願いします
&gt;&gt; Nice to meet you, too.
&gt;&gt; こちらこそよろしくお願いします